







Skills

FRONTEND

JavaScript, React, Context API, Redux, D3.js, Accessibility, Material-UI, Tailwind, Bootstrap, TypeScript.

BACKEND

Python, Django, Flask, Node.js, Express.js, Next.js, GraphQL, REST API.

DATABASES

Firebase, MongoDB, PostgreSQL.

TESTING

Jest, React Testing Library.

DEVOPS

Bash, Docker, GitHub Actions.

CLOUD

AWS

BASIC KNOWLEDGE

Java, Spring.

OTHER

Shopify, Sanity, Wordpress.

Languages

English - Fluent

Finnish - Novice Vietnamese - Native

Accomplishments

Participated in Geebiz 2018, a global contest in leadership, cross-cultural communication, social entrepreneurship and international business

Cuong Vu

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Vantaa, Finland (based in Vantaa, but able to relocate everywhere within Finland or Europe)

Cuong is an up-and-coming Full Stack Developer who has proven his abilities in action. Cuong has already worked in an e-commerce company as well as building websites for customers. In addition to his skill set in web development, Cuong is a recent graduate with a B.B.A. degree in International Business. He has pursuits in marketing, leadership, and social entrepreneurship. This rare blend of backgrounds enables Cuong to understand the business objectives and use cases behind his work as a developer.

Experience

Mehtaheino | Espoo, Finland | May 2022 - September 2022

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



- Developed an e-commerce website project for the firm using React, Node.js, and other Micro service technologies.
- Designed a scaleable web-based application structure and worked with other developers to deliver the web service on time.
- Communicated with UI designer, sales team and content creator for efficient workflow.
- Worked with DevOps practices (Bash scripting, Docker containers, and CI/CD with GitHub Actions) and Cloud Services with AWS.

<u>Integrify | Helsinki, Finland | October 2021 - February 2022</u>

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



- Sharpening competence as a Full Stack Developer by collaborating with other developers of different seniorities on a diverse range of projects and real-life challenges.
- Focusing on front-end development with JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Redux in addition to other technologies and concepts such as accessibility and animations.
- Building back-end for web-based applications with frameworks such as Node.js and Express.is.
- Covering additional concepts such as API development and documentation, unit testing with Jest, SQL and NoSQL databases, and version control with GitHub.
- Working with DevOps practices (Bash scripting, Docker containers, and CI/CD with GitHub Actions) and Cloud Services with AWS.

Yield Systems Oy | Espoo, Finland | March 2021 - July 2021

WEB DEVELOPER TRAINEE



- Collaborated with other team members to ideate and deliver projects on a quarterly
- Worked closely with a senior developer to provide a qualified and professional UI.
- Applied industrial standard languages such as Javascript, HTML, CSS to a internal web application project.

redWEB ApS | Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam | January 2020 - July 2020

FRONTEND DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP



- · Developed an internal project for the firm using React.js, JavaScript, and other Micro frontend technologies to store learning documents and engage among each other.
- Collaborated with 10 team members including a scrum master and project owner to ideate and deliver projects on a quarterly basis.
- Contributed to the annual income of the company's revenue of €2.5 million euros by delivering internal projects and shadowing lead developers on large projects.

Page: 1/2

Thinh Vu Phu Kien | Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam | February 2019 - August 2019

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER



- Developed a website with WordPress for an e-commerce company consisting of five primary members focusing on the sales of smartphones and accessories leading to a monthly revenue of 135 million Vietnamese Dong (VND).
- Created several content materials for the website by benchmarking from the top 10 e-commerce platforms in Asia to generate monthly sales for the company.
- Managed paid and organic marketing on Google and Facebook using their advertising platforms on a total budget of 5 million VND.

RECENT PROJECTS

Github User Finder App





React.js, AuthO, Fusion charts, Context API

This project allows users to search any Github user profile. Main features include authentication powered by authO and api provided from github.

E-commerce Store





React.js, AuthO, Stripe, ContextAPI, Netlify CLI

Ecommerce website which utilizes Stripe for payment service, AuthO for authentication. The main skeleton of state management is Context API

Job Search Application





React.js, JWT, MongoDB, Redux, Heroku, Node.js, Express.js

Job search website with CRUD, authentication, authorization system, and analysis dashboard. This project is a good case to prove my skills with MERN stack. I have followed a good old traditional design convention of MERN to make this website livable.

Blog Application





React.js, JWT, MongoDB, Context API, Heroku, Node.js, Express.js

Blog website with authentication, which allow user to add, delete, update, review and update their own information.

Social App





React.js, Firebase

This social app are created by React and Firebase. This project gives me an opportunity to discover firebase service from start to very end.

EDUCATION

B.B.A. IN INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS



LAB University of Applied Sciences | Lappeenranta, Finland | August 2017 - December 2020

Page: 2/2